Hi again.
This module featured a lot of information.
We revisited familiar concepts and
introduced so many new ones.
We discussed quality management, where
we learned the four steps to ensuring
quality, which includes setting
quality standards, quality planning,
quality assurance, and quality control.
We covered continuous improvement and
how to use data driven strategies such
as DMAIC, which stands for Define,
Measure, Analyze, Improve, Control.
And PDCA, which stands for
Plan, Do, Check,
act in order to work toward
continuous improvements.
We learned how to conduct and
use retrospectives as a tool for
future improvements.
And how to facilitate positive
conversation and encourage feedback
from your team members in order to avoid
mistakes later on in future projects.
I'm really proud of how far you've come,
and I hope you are too.
I hope you take a moment to admire
your progress and applaud yourself.
In the next module, you'll learn about
the importance of gathering data and
how to make data driven decisions.
I'll meet you there whenever you're ready.